Time has come to listen to the crying of their puppet souls
kimi ga sonna ni motto raku wo shite
君がそんなにもっと楽をして
ikidzumatta mirai to aizu
行き詰まった未来と合図
Words are strong, heart is dropped,
scatter around and falls
itsuwari no contact-everything
偽りのcontact-everything
sasoikonda kizu ga mazaru
誘い込んだ傷が混ざる
daremo wasureta kanashimi ga fall out
誰も忘れた悲しみが　fall out
gimei wa tada kooru kibou no jirenma
偽名はただ凍る　希望のジレンマ
iki sogiotosu kodou mo osaeru
息削ぎ落とす行動も抑える
sou wakatteiru kotae nado sutete shimae
そう解っている答えなど捨ててしまえ
Yeah get started breaking the row
See how it spreads out. It's beyond full realization
Yeah get started re-creating the world
Take my hands till the end, feel this raw emotion
bring it on down rock rock rock
shake it up up tap top top
cuz I know how to shout out my soul
bring it on down rock rock rock
shake it up up tap top top
cuz you know how to shout out your soul
Time has come to listen to the crying of their puppet souls